{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Barberousse",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance directed Barberousse.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8653761744499207,
            "question": "Who directed the film Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7976157665252686,
            "question": "Who is the director behind Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7944881319999695,
            "question": "Which director is known for making Barberousse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7570431232452393,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7198928594589233,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Abel Gance."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6777624487876892,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.635590136051178,
            "question": "What film did Abel Gance direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5932697057723999,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5361916422843933,
            "question": "What was the title of Abel Gance's film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40727004408836365,
            "question": "What kind of work did Abel Gance create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance directed Barberousse.",
            "html": "yago_4178_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the title of Abel Gance's film?",
            "html": "yago_4178_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a film directed by Abel Gance?",
            "html": "yago_4178_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Abel Gance direct?",
            "html": "yago_4178_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4178_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because according to the context information, Abel Gance directed the silent French film \"Barberousse\" (1917), and there are multiple mentions of this fact in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Abel Gance was a French film director and that he directed the 1917 silent film \"Barberousse.\" Therefore, the triple \"Abel Gance directed Barberousse\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}